var names = ["Cleo", "Deborah", "Stella", "L", "Katrina", "Esther", "Deborah"]
var questionList = [
  [
    {
      question: "Name a Canadaian province",
      wrong: "Huron-Wendat",
      correct: ["Prince Edward Island", "Nova Scotia", "Saskatchewan", "Newfoundland and Labrador", "New Brunswick", "Manitoba"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name someone born before 1900",
      wrong: "Lyndon B. Johnson",
      correct: ["Albert Einstein", "Harry S. Truman", "Winston Churchill", "Thomas Edison", "Helen Keller", "Colonel Sanders"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name an Austin Powers character",
      wrong: "Mike Oxsmall",
      correct: ["Number 2", "Scott Evil", "Fook Mi", "Robin Swallows", "Fat Bastard", "General Borschevsky"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name an ultimate ability from League of Legends",
      wrong: "Shadow Flare",
      correct: ["Unbreakable Will", "Voice of Light", "Glacial Fissure", "Hextech Ultimatum", "Last Caress", "Cataclysm"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a video game released for the Nintendo Wii",
      wrong: "LSD: Dream Emulator",
      correct: ["Call of Duty: Black Ops", "Wii Chess", "Enjoy your Massage!", "Anubis 2", "Alvin and the Chipmunks", "Dragonball Z Budokai Tenkaichi 3"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a United States involvement with regime change",
      wrong: "Madagascar",
      correct: ["South Korea", "Iran", "Indonesia", "Nicaragua", "Laos", "Brazil"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a former president of the Philippines",
      wrong: "Yingluck Shinawatra",
      correct: ["Emilio Aguinaldo", "Manuel L. Quezon", "Jose P. Laurel", "Sergio Osme√±a", "Manuel Roxas", "Ramon Magsaysay"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a Taylor Swift Song",
      wrong: "Besties",
      correct: ["Better Than Revenge", "Ivy", "Change", "Betty", "Starlight", "Long Story Short"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a dog breed",
      wrong: "Moroccan Griffon",
      correct: ["Basset Hound", "Australian Shepherd", "Maltipoo", "Chow Chow", "Afghan Hound", "Portuguese Water Dog"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name one of the Apostles in the New Testament",
      wrong: "Joseph",
      correct: ["Bartholomew", "James", "Philip", "Matthew", "Andrew", "Simon"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a word invented by Shakespeare",
      wrong: "Weary",
      correct: ["Skim-milk", "Swagger", "Unaware", "Undress", "Critic", "Lonely"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name an anime",
      wrong: "Watashi no Oshiri ga Ookii!",
      correct: ["Gintama", "Clannad", "Owarimonogatari", "Monster", "Sen to Chihiro no Kamikakushi", "Berserk"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a romanized line from Gangnam Style",
      wrong: "allanggamolla wae hwakkeunhaeya haneungeonji",
      correct: ["naneun mwol jom aneun nom", "jeongsukhae boijiman nol ttaen noneun yeoja", "ttaega doemyeon wanjeon michyeobeorineun sanai", "ttwineun nom geu wie naneun nom", "kopi hanjanui yeoyureul aneun pumgyeok inneun yeoja", "areumdawo sarangseureowo"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a character from The Office",
      wrong: "Paul Keaton",
      correct: ["Holly Flax", "David Wallace", "Darryl Philbin", "Jan Levinson", "Karen Filippelli", "Hidetoshi Hasagawa"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name an AP course or exam offered by CollegeBoard",
      wrong: "AP Veterinary Science",
      correct: ["AP Art History", "AP Comparative Government and Politics", "AP Music Theory", "AP Latin", "AP Physics C: Mechanics", "Studio Art: 3-D Design"],
    },
    {
      question: "Name a territory that gained independence from the United Kingdom",
      wrong: "Ethiopia",
      correct: ["Myanmar", "Fiji", "Zanzibar", "Malaya", "Iraq", "Egypt"],
    },
    {
      question: "Asian Americans",
      wrong: "Mark Lee",
      correct: ["Elaine Chao", "Zach King", "Roger H. Chen", "Perry Chen", "Ellen Pao", "Ken Jeong"],
    }
  ]
];